export const pollData = [
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'What is your favorite color?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['red', 'blue', 'green', 'yellow'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'Do you use the library to study?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 1,
    answers: ['all the time', 'sometimes', 'rarely', 'never'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'How many hours do you study a day?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['0 to 1', '2 to 3', '4 to 5', 'more than 5'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'Do you play video games?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 2,
    answers: ['yes', 'no'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText:
      'On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate your writing skills? (1 being poor, 10 being excellent)',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4', '5', '6', '7', '8', '9', '10'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText:
      'On a scale of 1 to 10, how would you rate your mathematical skills? (1 being poor, 10 being excellent)',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 3,
    answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4', '5', '6', '7', '8', '9', '10'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText:
      'Which country in Europe do you most want to visit for a holiday?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: ['Spain', 'France', 'Germany', 'Italy', 'United Kingdom'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'What activity do you enjoy most when on holiday?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 4,
    answers: [
      'shopping',
      'sight seeing',
      'eating and drinking',
      'meeting new people',
      'staying in the hotel',
    ],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText:
      'After this class, will you use data visualizations more or less in your other classes?',
    questionNumber: 1,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: ['more', 'less'],
  },
  {
    category: 'poll',
    questionText: 'What is your favorite type of data visualization?',
    questionNumber: 2,
    weekNumber: 5,
    answers: [
      'column/bar chart',
      'pie chart',
      'scatter plot',
      'geographic (choropleth)',
      'line chart',
      'highlight table',
      'other',
    ],
  },
];
